so let's discuss the speed up numbers we
can get we have already seen in the
previous quizzes that a speed up larger
than one means improve performance
either through shorter execution time it
takes less to compute something than
before or higher throughput we can do
more of something per second than before
a speed up of less than one means that
we have worse performance than before
either it takes longer to execute
something or we get lower throughput
than before and finally when Computing
speed up remember that performance is
proportional to throughput so when
Computing speed up we divide the
throughput of the new thing with the
throughput of the old thing however
performance is proportional to one over
latency so if we have something like it
takes two seconds to do something that's
a latency performance in this case is
one over that so when Computing speed
UPS we actually divide the old latency
with the new latency